Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Photographs of Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of Individuals, 1870-1972; Series I
  - Hubbard, Otis L. (Box 38, Folder 1658)
  - Hubbard, Richard D. (Box 38, Folder 1659)
  - Hubbard, Stephen B. (Box 38, Folder 1660)
  - Hubbard, Walter R. (Box 38, Folder 1661)
  - Hubbell, Harry M. (Box 38, Folder 1662)
  - Huber, Matthew J. (Box 38, Folder 1663)
  - Hu-Ching-Yu (Box 38, Folder 1664)
  - Huckaby, Reuben J. (Box 38, Folder 1665)
  - Hucko, Grace (Box 38, Folder 1666)
  - Hudnutt, Dean (Box 38, Folder 1667)
  - Huffman, Franklin E. (Box 38, Folder 1668)
  - Huggins, T. (Box 38, Folder 1669)
  - Hughes, Emmett John (Box 38, Folder 1670)
  - Hughes, Forrest A. (Box 38, Folder 1671)
  - Hughes, Vernon (Box 38, Folder 1672)
  - Huhn, John Bell (Box 38, Folder 1673)
  - Hukill, Peter B. (Box 38, Folder 1674)
  - Hull, Clark L. (Box 38, Folder 1675)
  - Hummel, David M. (Box 38, Folder 1676)
  - Humphrey, George (Box 38, Folder 1677)
  - Humphrey, Hubert (Box 38, Folder 1678)
  - Humphrey, Phillip S. (Box 38, Folder 1679)
  - Hunt, Carlton C. (Box 38, Folder 1680)
  - Hunt, Michael Houston (Box 38, Folder 1681)
  - Hunter, James H. Jr. (Box 38, Folder 1682)
  - Huntington, Benjamin (Box 38, Folder 1683)
  - Huntington, Samuel (Box 38, Folder 1684)
  - Huntington, Willard B. (Box 38, Folder 1685)
  - Hurd, Fredrick W. (Box 38, Folder 1686)
  - Hurwit, Jeffrey M. (Box 38, Folder 1687)
  - Huston, J. Daniels (Box 38, Folder 1688)
  - Hutchins, Francis S. (Box 38, Folder 1689)
  - Hutchins, Robert M. (Box 38, Folder 1690)
  - Hutchinson, Franklin (Box 38, Folder 1691)
  - Hutchinson, G. Evelyn (Box 39, Folder 1692)
  - Hutchinson, William (Box 39, Folder 1693)
  - Hutter, Robert Victor Paul (Box 39, Folder 1694)
  - Hyatt, ----- (Box 39, Folder 1695)
  - Hyde, Charles C. (Box 39, Folder 1696)
  - Hyder, Kate O. (Box 39, Folder 1697)
  - Hyman, ----- (Box 39, Folder 1698)
  - Hymer, Stephen H. (Box 39, Folder 1699)
  - Ichard, ----- (Box 39, Folder 1700)
  - Illich, Ivan (Box 39, Folder 1701)
  - Ingalls, David S. (Box 39, Folder 1702)
  - Ingersoll, Charles R. (Box 39, Folder 1703)
  - Ingholt, Harald (Box 39, Folder 1704)
  - Irland, Lloyd C. (Box 39, Folder 1705)
  - Irving, Richard R. (Box 39, Folder 1706)
  - Irwin, Donald J. (Box 39, Folder 1707)
  - Irwin, I. (Box 39, Folder 1708)
  - Isaacson, Larry (Box 39, Folder 1709)
  - Isleib, Horace F. (Box 39, Folder 1710)
  - Israel, Richard J. (Box 39, Folder 1711)
  - Ives, Charles L. (Box 39, Folder 1712)
  - Ives, Eli (Box 39, Folder 1713)
  - Izenour, George C. (Box 39, Folder 1714)
  - Jackson, C. D. (Box 39, Folder 1715)
  - Jackson, Edith B. (Box 39, Folder 1716-17)
  - Jackson, Holmes (Box 39, Folder 1718)
  - Jackson, John Henrik (Box 39, Folder 1719)
  - Jackson, Joseph F. (Box 39, Folder 1720)
  - Jackson, Robert L. (Box 39, Folder 1721)
  - Jackson, Thomas H. (Box 39, Folder 1722)
  - Jacobson, George H. (Box 39, Folder 1723)
  - Jacobson, Nathan (Box 39, Folder 1724)
  - Jacunski, Harry (Box 39, Folder 1725)
  - James, ----- (Box 39, Folder 1726)
  - James, Alan T. (Box 39, Folder 1727)
  - James, David G. (Box 39, Folder 1728)
  - James, Fleming (Box 39, Folder 1729)
  - Jameson, Fredric (Box 39, Folder 1730)
  - Janis, Irving L. (Box 39, Folder 1731)
  - Januska, Charlotte (Box 39, Folder 1732)
  - Janzen, Arnold H. (Box 39, Folder 1733)
  - Jarrel, Randall (Box 39, Folder 1734)
  - Jasinski, Frank J. (Box 39, Folder 1735)
  - Javits, Jacob: Senator (Box 39, Folder 1736)
  - Jenkins, Iredell (Box 39, Folder 1737)
  - Jenkins, Roy (Box 39, Folder 1738)
  - Jenks, Ruth C. (Box 39, Folder 1739)
  - Jennings, B. Brewster (Box 40, Folder 1740)
  - Jensen, ----- (Box 40, Folder 1741)
  - Jensen, Russell C. (Box 40, Folder 1742)
  - Jensen, Meade L. (Box 40, Folder 1743)
  - Jepsen, Harry B. (Box 40, Folder 1744)
  - "Jerry" (Box 40, Folder 1745)
  - Jervis, Jane (Box 40, Folder 1746)
  - Jessup, ----- (Box 40, Folder 1747)
  - Jewett, C. W.: Lt. Governor (Box 40, Folder 1748)
  - Johnson, Alvin H. (Box 40, Folder 1749)
  - Johnson, Alvin S. (Box 40, Folder 1750)
  - Johnson, Andrew E. (Box 40, Folder 1751)
  - Johnson, Charles S., Jr. (Box 40, Folder 1752)
  - Johnson, Clint (Box 40, Folder 1753)
  - Johnson, Dave (Box 40, Folder 1754)
  - Johnson, Diodate (Box 40, Folder 1755)
  - Johnson, Frederic B. (Box 40, Folder 1756)
  - Johnson, Harry G. (Box 40, Folder 1757)
  - Johnson, -----: Judge (Box 40, Folder 1758)
  - Johnson, Lyndon (Box 40, Folder 1759)
  - Johnson, Luci Baines (Box 40, Folder 1760)
  - Johnson, Lynda Barid (Box 40, Folder 1761)
  - Johnson, Philip (Box 40, Folder 1762)
  - Johnson, Robert Clyde (Box 40, Folder 1763)
  - Johnson, Ronald (Box 40, Folder 1764)
  - Johnson, Samuel, Y. 1714 (Box 40, Folder 1765)
  - Johnson, Samuel W. (Box 40, Folder 1766)
  - Johnson, -----: Senator (Box 40, Folder 1767)
  - Johnson, Tony (Box 40, Folder 1768)
  - Johnson, Treat B. (Box 40, Folder 1769)
  - Johnson, Willie (Box 40, Folder 1770)
  - Johnson, Winford B. (Box 40, Folder 1771)
  - Johnston, Eric (Box 40, Folder 1772)
  - Johnston, Waldo C. (Box 40, Folder 1773)
  - Johnstone, Quintin (Box 40, Folder 1774)
  - Jonas, Albert M. (Box 40, Folder 1775)
  - Jones, Elisha C. (Box 40, Folder 1776)
  - Jones, Frederick S. (Box 40, Folder 1777)
  - Jones, Hugh-Lloyd (Box 40, Folder 1778)
  - Jones, Jack B. (Box 40, Folder 1779)
  - Jones, Paul B. (Box 40, Folder 1780)
  - Jones, Paul M. (Box 40, Folder 1781)
  - Jones, Ralph C. (Box 40, Folder 1782)
  - Jones, Richard O. (Box 40, Folder 1783)
  - Jones, Stephen B. (Box 40, Folder 1784)
  - Jones, Tim W. (Box 40, Folder 1785)
  - Jones, Tony (Box 40, Folder 1786)
  - Jones, William Hamilton (Box 40, Folder 1787)
  - Jones, William R. (Box 40, Folder 1788)
  - Jordan, Peter A. (Box 40, Folder 1789)
  - Jordan, Richard G. (Box 40, Folder 1790)
  - Jordan (?), Vernon (Box 40, Folder 1791)
  - Jordy, William H. (Box 40, Folder 1792)
  - Jory, Jon (Box 40, Folder 1793)
  - Josephs, ----- (Box 40, Folder 1794)
  - Josephs, Devreux (Box 40, Folder 1795)
  - Joyner, T. Craig (Box 40, Folder 1796)
  - Jubin, Brenda L. (Box 40, Folder 1797)
  - Judd, Walter (Box 40, Folder 1798)
  - Justusson, William J. (Box 40, Folder 1799)
  - Kael, Pauline (Box 41, Folder 1800)
  - Kaetz, Harvey W., M.D. (Box 41, Folder 1801)
  - Kagan, Donald (Box 41, Folder 1802)
  - Kahn, Eugen (Box 41, Folder 1803)
  - Kahn, Fred S. (Box 41, Folder 1804)
  - Kahn, Herman: Associate Librarian for Manuscripts and Archives (Box 41, Folder 1805)
  - Kahn, Herman: Director, Hudson Institute (Box 41, Folder 1806)
  - Kahn, Louis I. (Box 41, Folder 1807)
  - Kahn, Michael (Box 41, Folder 1808)
  - Kahn-Freund, Otto (Box 41, Folder 1809)
  - Kakutani, Shizuo (Box 41, Folder 1810)
  - Kantor, Peter (Box 41, Folder 1811)
  - Kanzler, Robert H. (Box 41, Folder 1812)
  - Kaplan, Louis J. (Box 41, Folder 1813)
  - Kaplan, Mortimer (Box 41, Folder 1814)
  - Kaplan, Morton (Box 41, Folder 1815)
  - Kappel, Frederick R. (Box 41, Folder 1816)
  - Karenga, Ron (Box 41, Folder 1817)
  - Kase, Nathan G. (Box 41, Folder 1818)
  - Kaselon, Joseph (Box 41, Folder 1819)
  - Kasemann, Ernest (Box 41, Folder 1820)
  - Kastenmeier, Robert W. (Box 41, Folder 1821)
  - Katz, Eve G. (Box 41, Folder 1822)
  - Katz, Jay (Box 41, Folder 1823)
  - Katz, Joel (Box 41, Folder 1824)
  - Katzenbach, Nicholas deB. (Box 41, Folder 1825)
  - Kauffman, Stanley (Box 41, Folder 1826)
  - Kafman, ----- (Box 41, Folder 1827)
  - Kaufman, Herbert (Box 41, Folder 1828)
  - Kazemzadeh, Firuz (Box 41, Folder 1829)
  - Keach, Dewitt T. (Box 41, Folder 1830)
  - Keator, Frederic W. (Box 41, Folder 1831)
  - Keele, Kenneth D. (Box 41, Folder 1832)
  - Keene, Donald (Box 41, Folder 1833)
  - Kefauver, Estes (Box 41, Folder 1834)
  - Keggi, Kristaps J. (Box 41, Folder 1835)
  - Kehane, T. J. (Box 41, Folder 1836)
  - Kehm, George H. (Box 41, Folder 1837)
  - Keith, Robbie (Box 41, Folder 1838)
  - Kellems, Vivian (Box 41, Folder 1839)
  - Keller, Albert G. (Box 41, Folder 1840)
  - Keller, Deane (Box 41, Folder 1841)
  - Keller, Florence (Box 41, Folder 1842)
  - Keller, John P. (Box 41, Folder 1843)
  - Kelley, Alva E. (Box 41, Folder 1844)
  - Kelley, Brooks M. (Box 41, Folder 1845)
  - Kelley, Larry (Box 41, Folder 1846)
  - Kellogg, Martin (Box 41, Folder 1847)
  - Kelsney, Erwin B. (Box 41, Folder 1848)
  - Kelson, Itzhak (Box 41, Folder 1849)
  - Kempton, ----- (Box 41, Folder 1850)
  - Kendall, Willmore M., Jr. (Box 41, Folder 1851)
  - Kendrick, Wilmer M., Jr. (Box 41, Folder 1852)
  - Kenefick, J. Gordon (Box 41, Folder 1853)
  - Keniston, Kenneth (Box 41, Folder 1854)
  - Kenna, George F. (Box 41, Folder 1855)
  - Kennedy, George A. (Box 41, Folder 1856)
  - Kennedy, John F. (Box 41, Folder 1857)
  - Kennedy, Julian (Box 41, Folder 1858)
  - Kennedy, Raymond (Box 41, Folder 1859)
  - Kennedy, Robert F. (Box 41, Folder 1860)
  - Kenney, Robert (Box 42, Folder 1861)
  - Kent, Charles F. (Box 42, Folder 1862)
  - Kent, Sherman (Box 42, Folder 1863)
  - Keogh, Andrew (Box 42, Folder 1864)
  - Kerensky, Alexander (Box 42, Folder 1865)
  - Kernan, Alvin B. (Box 42, Folder 1866)
  - Kerouac, Jack (Box 42, Folder 1867)
  - Kerr, Chester B. (Box 42, Folder 1868)
  - Kerr, Edith (Mrs. Chester B.) (Box 42, Folder 1869)
  - Kerr, Walter (Box 42, Folder 1870)
  - Kerry, John (Box 42, Folder 1871)
  - Kershaw, F. (Box 42, Folder 1872)
  - Kerstetter, Bert (Box 42, Folder 1873)
  - Kertesz, Istvan (Box 42, Folder 1874)
  - Kessen, William (Box 42, Folder 1875)
  - Kessler, Frerich (Box 42, Folder 1876)
  - Key, Valdimer O. (Box 42, Folder 1877)
  - Kezerian, Stephen A. (Box 42, Folder 1878)
  - Khan, Sir Zafrullah (Box 42, Folder 1879)
  - Kiefer, Jack (Box 42, Folder 1880)
  - Kiely, Daniel H. (Box 42, Folder 1881)
  - Kierstead, Raymond F. (Box 42, Folder 1882)
  - Kilgour, Frederick G. (Box 42, Folder 1883)
  - Killen, William (Box 42, Folder 1884)
  - Killian, James (Box 42, Folder 1885)
  - Kilpatrick, William (Box 42, Folder 1886)
  - Kindlmann, Peter Juergen (Box 42, Folder 1887)
  - King, Edwin B. (Box 42, Folder 1888)
  - King, Eleanor M. (Box 42, Folder 1889)
  - King, Coretta (Box 42, Folder 1890)
  - Kinlock, Hector G. (Box 42, Folder 1891)
  - Kinnell, Galway (Box 42, Folder 1892)
  - Kiphuth, Delaney (Box 42, Folder 1893)
  - Kiphuth, Oscar W. (Box 42, Folder 1894)
  - Kiphuth, Robert J. H. (Box 42, Folder 1895)
  - Kirby, Edward (Box 42, Folder 1896)
  - Kirchner, John A. (Box 42, Folder 1897)
  - Kirk, Geoffrey S. (Box 42, Folder 1898)
  - Kirk, Govenor (Box 42, Folder 1899)
  - Kirk, Grayson (Box 42, Folder 1900)
  - Kirk, Russell (Box 42, Folder 1901)
  - Kirk, Venderveer (Box 42, Folder 1902)
  - Kirkpatric, Ralph (Box 42, Folder 1903)
  - Kirkwood, John G. (Box 42, Folder 1904)
  - Kirshbaum, Ralph (Box 43, Folder 1905)
  - Kistler, Alan L. (Box 43, Folder 1906)
  - Klatskin, Gerald (Box 43, Folder 1907)
  - Klaus, Sidney (Box 43, Folder 1908)
  - Klein, Herb (Box 43, Folder 1909)
  - Klein, Mahlon (Box 43, Folder 1910)
  - Klein, Martin J. (Box 43, Folder 1911)
  - Kleinberg, Donald R. (Box 43, Folder 1912)
  - Kleiman, Harlan P. (Box 43, Folder 1913)
  - Klevorick, Alvin K. (Box 43, Folder 1914)
  - Kligerman, Morton M. (Box 43, Folder 1915)
  - Knapp, Janet E. (Box 43, Folder 1916)
  - Knapp, William I. (Box 43, Folder 1917)
  - Kneen, John (Box 43, Folder 1918)
  - Knight, Douglas M. (Box 43, Folder 1919)
  - Knight, Jonathon (Box 43, Folder 1920)
  - Knight, Robert H., Jr. (Box 43, Folder 1921)
  - Knite, ----- (Box 43, Folder 1922)
  - Knollenberg, Bernhard (Box 43, Folder 1923)
  - Knopf, Adoplh (Box 43, Folder 1924)
  - Knorr, Klaus E. (Box 43, Folder 1925)
  - Knowles, Ellis (Box 43, Folder 1926)
  - Knowles, H. C. (Box 43, Folder 1927)
  - Knowles, John (Box 43, Folder 1928)
  - Knowlton, Archer E. (Box 43, Folder 1929)
  - Knox, Bernard M. W. (Box 43, Folder 1930)
  - Knox, John (Box 43, Folder 1931)
  - Knox, Seymour (Box 43, Folder 1932)
  - Knox, William J. (Box 43, Folder 1933)
  - Koener, S. John (Box 43, Folder 1934)
  - Koevago, Joseph (Box 43, Folder 1935)
  - Kohler, Walter (Box 43, Folder 1936)
  - Kok, Gerard P. (Box 43, Folder 1937)
  - Kokeritz, Helge (Box 43, Folder 1938)
  - Kolesov, Vladimer V. (Box 43, Folder 1939)
  - Kone, Elliot H. (Box 43, Folder 1940)
  - Kone, Eugene H. (Box 43, Folder 1940)
  - Koopmans, Joan (Box 43, Folder 1942)
  - Koopmans, Tjalling C. (Box 43, Folder 1943)
  - Kornfield, H. Allen (Box 43, Folder 1944)
  - Kortschak, Hugo (Box 43, Folder 1945)
  - Kortt, S. R. (Box 43, Folder 1946)
  - Koskoff, Yale David (Box 43, Folder 1947)
  - Kott, Jan (Box 43, Folder 1948)
  - Kotz, D. (Box 43, Folder 1949)
  - Kovarik, Alois F. (Box 43, Folder 1950)
  - Kozol, ----- (Box 43, Folder 1951)
  - Kraehenbeuhl, David (Box 43, Folder 1952)
  - Kraeling, Carl H. (Box 43, Folder 1953)
  - Kraemer, Joel L. (Box 43, Folder 1954)
  - Kraft, Lisbeth M. (Box 43, Folder 1955)
  - Kramer, Gerald H. (Box 43, Folder 1956)
  - Krause, Lawrence (Box 43, Folder 1957)
  - Krauss, Herbert L. (Box 43, Folder 1958)
  - Krawitz, Herman E. (Box 43, Folder 1959)
  - Krehl, Willard A. (Box 43, Folder 1960)
  - Kreisky, Bruno (Box 43, Folder 1961)
  - Kreiger, Leonard (Box 44, Folder 1962)
  - Krigbaum, Charles R. (Box 44, Folder 1963)
  - Kripalani, ----- (Box 44, Folder 1964)
  - Krizek, Thomas J. (Box 44, Folder 1965)
  - Kruman, John M. (Box 44, Folder 1966)
  - Krynine, Dimitri P. (Box 44, Folder 1967)
  - Kubitschek, J. (Box 44, Folder 1968)
  - Kubler, George A. (Box 44, Folder 1969)
  - Kuchel, Thomas (Senator) (Box 44, Folder 1970)
  - Kuehn, Robert E. (Box 44, Folder 1971)
  - Kuh, Clifford (Box 44, Folder 1972)
  - Kulsrud, Russell M. (Box 44, Folder 1973)
  - Kung, Hans (Box 44, Folder 1974)
  - Kunitz, Stanley (Box 44, Folder 1975)
  - Kunstler, William (Box 44, Folder 1976)
  - Kury, Gloria (Box 44, Folder 1977)
  - Kusteren, Ken (Box 44, Folder 1978)
  - Kuttner, Stephan G. (Box 44, Folder 1979)
  - Kutz, Herbert M. (Box 44, Folder 1980)
  - Kydd, David M. (Box 44, Folder 1981)
  - Labaree, Leonard W. (Box 44, Folder 1982)
  - Lach, Joseph T. (Box 44, Folder 1983)
  - Ladd, Edward T. (Box 44, Folder 1984)
  - Ladd, George T. (Box 44, Folder 1985)
  - La Frazier, Elizabeth (Box 44, Folder 1986)
  - Laird, Melvin (Box 44, Folder 1987)
  - Laise, Carol C. (Box 44, Folder 1988)
  - Lam, George L. (Box 44, Folder 1989)
  - Lamar, Howard R. (Box 44, Folder 1990)
  - Lamb, Lomax B. (Box 44, Folder 1991)
  - Lamb, Sydney M. (Box 44, Folder 1992)
  - Lamb, Ursula S. (Box 44, Folder 1993)
  - Lamb, Willis E. (Box 44, Folder 1994)
  - Lamport, Harold (Box 44, Folder 1995)
  - Lancaster, ----- (Box 44, Folder 1996)
  - Land, Edwin (Box 44, Folder 1997)
  - Lande, Saul (Box 44, Folder 1998)
  - Lane, Arthur Bliss (Box 44, Folder 1999)
  - Lane, Cecil T. (Box 44, Folder 2000)
  - Lane, Mark (Box 44, Folder 2001)
  - Lane, Robert E. (Box 44, Folder 2002)
  - Lang, Henry Roseman (Box 44, Folder 2003)
  - Langdon, George D., Jr. (Box 44, Folder 2004)
  - La Palombara, Joseph (Box 44, Folder 2005)
  - Lardy, Nicholas R. (Box 44, Folder 2006)
  - Larned, Joseph G. E. (Box 44, Folder 2007)
  - Larned, William A. (Box 44, Folder 2008)
  - Laslett, Peter (Box 44, Folder 2009)
  - Lasswell, Harold D. (Box 45, Folder 2010)
  - Lasty, George (Box 45, Folder 2011)
  - La Tourette, Kenneth S. (Box 45, Folder 2012)
  - Lattimore, Orwen (Box 45, Folder 2013)
  - Laub, Levi (Box 45, Folder 2014)
  - Laurie, Lee (Box 45, Folder 2015)
  - Laurson, Philip G. (Box 45, Folder 2016)
  - Lausche, Frank (Box 45, Folder 2017)
  - Lautner, Edward (Box 45, Folder 2018)
  - La Valley, Albert Joseph (Box 45, Folder 2019)
  - Lavandero, Leo (Box 45, Folder 2020)
  - Lavin, Linda (Box 45, Folder 2021)
  - Lawder, Standish D. (Box 45, Folder 2022)
  - Lawler, Edward (Box 45, Folder 2023)
  - Lawler, Greg (Box 45, Folder 2024)
  - Lawler, Traugott F. (Box 45, Folder 2025)
  - Lawrence, Edward A. (Box 45, Folder 2026)
  - Lawrence, Ernest O. (Box 45, Folder 2027)
  - Lawrence, Nathaniel (Box 45, Folder 2028)
  - Lawrence, William (Box 45, Folder 2029)
  - Lawton, robert F. (Box 45, Folder 2030)
  - Lea, Kenneth (Box 45, Folder 2031)
  - Leader, Edwin O. (Box 45, Folder 2032)
  - Leakey, Louis B. (Box 45, Folder 2033)
  - Leary, Howard (Box 45, Folder 2034)
  - Leatherwood, Thomas O. (Box 45, Folder 2035)
  - Leavy, Stanley A. (Box 45, Folder 2036)
  - Leburn, James G. (Box 45, Folder 2037)
  - Lederer, Albrecht M. (Box 45, Folder 2038)
  - Lederer, Ivo J. (Box 45, Folder 2039)
  - Ledig, F. Thomas (Box 45, Folder 2040)
  - Lee, Andrew (Box 45, Folder 2041)
  - Lee, David (Box 45, Folder 2042)
  - Lee, George J. (Box 45, Folder 2043)
  - Lee, J. B. (Box 45, Folder 2044)
  - Lee, John Y. (Box 45, Folder 2045)
  - Lee, Ray M. (Box 45, Folder 2046)
  - Lee, Richard C. (Box 45, Folder 2047)
  - Lee, Robert E. (Box 45, Folder 2048)
  - Leff, Arthur A. (Box 45, Folder 2049)
  - Lefkowitz, Louis K. (Box 45, Folder 2050)
  - Lehman, Paul (Box 45, Folder 2051)
  - Lehmann, Robert (Box 45, Folder 2052-53)
  - Lehmann-Haupt, Hellmut (Box 45, Folder 2054)
  - Leiken, Sam (Box 45, Folder 2055)
  - Leiserson, Mark W. (Box 45, Folder 2056)
  - Le May, Curtis (Box 45, Folder 2057)
  - Lemkin, Raphael (Box 45, Folder 2058)
  - Lemmon, Jack (Box 45, Folder 2059)
  - Lenahan, Charles B. (Box 45, Folder 2060)
  - Lengyel, Peter (Box 45, Folder 2061)
  - Leonard, Harry, Jr. (Box 45, Folder 2062)
  - Leonhard, Wolfgang (Box 45, Folder 2063)
  - Leowski, Walter (Box 46, Folder 2064)
  - Lepper, Henry A., Jr. (Box 46, Folder 2065)
  - Lepper, Susan (Box 46, Folder 2066)
  - Lerner, Aaron B. (Box 46, Folder 2067)
  - Lerner, Max (Box 46, Folder 2068)
  - Lester, David (Box 46, Folder 2069)
  - Lester, Frankie (Box 46, Folder 2070)
  - Le Vine, Robert T. (Box 46, Folder 2071)
  - Levinson, Daniel J. (Box 46, Folder 2072)
  - Levit, Harry M. (Box 46, Folder 2073)
  - Levitin, Howard (Box 46, Folder 2074)
  - Levitt, Ralph (Box 46, Folder 2075)
  - Levmore, Saul (Box 46, Folder 2076)
  - Lewis, Cecil Day (Box 46, Folder 2077)
  - Lewis, Charlton M. (Box 46, Folder 2078)
  - Lewis, H. D. (Box 46, Folder 2079)
  - Lewis, John (Box 46, Folder 2080)
  - Lewis, John E. (Box 46, Folder 2081)
  - Lewis, Naphtali (Box 46, Folder 2082)
  - Lewis, Richard W. B. (Box 46, Folder 2083)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S. (Box 46, Folder 2084)
  - Li, Tien-Yi (Box 46, Folder 2085)
  - Libbey, Dennis A (Box 46, Folder 2086)
  - Lichten, William L. (Box 46, Folder 2087)
  - Lichty, Lester C. (Box 46, Folder 2088)
  - Lidz, Theodore (Box 46, Folder 2089)
  - Lieb, I. (Box 46, Folder 2090)
  - Lieberman, Joseph I. (Box 46, Folder 2091)
  - Liebert, Herman W. (Box 46, Folder 2092)
  - Liebman, Lance M. (Box 46, Folder 2093)
  - Liebman, Ron (Box 46, Folder 2094)
  - Liebow, Averill A. (Box 46, Folder 2095)
  - Lifton, Norman (Box 46, Folder 2096)
  - Lifton, Robert J. (Box 46, Folder 2097)
  - Lightfoot, Richard B. (Box 46, Folder 2098)
  - Lilley, A. Edward (Box 46, Folder 2099)
  - Lilley, William, III (Box 46, Folder 2100)
  - Limerick, Jeffrey (Box 46, Folder 2101)
  - Lindbeck, Assar (Box 46, Folder 2102)
  - Lindbeck, George A. (Box 46, Folder 2103)
  - Lindbeck, John M. H. (Box 46, Folder 2104)
  - Lindblom, Charles E. (Box 46, Folder 2105)
  - Linderblum, ----- (Box 46, Folder 2106)
  - Lindley, Ernest K. (Box 46, Folder 2107)
  - Lindsay, Michael F. M. (Box 46, Folder 2108)
  - Lindskog, Gustaf E. (Box 46, Folder 2109)
  - Lindsley, Charles A. (Box 47, Folder 2110)
  - Linen, James A. (Box 47, Folder 2111)
  - Linton, Ralph (Box 47, Folder 2112)
  - Lipari, A. (Box 47, Folder 2113)
  - Lippard, Vernon W. (Box 47, Folder 2114)
  - Lippincott, Lincoln H. (Box 47, Folder 2115)
  - Lipskey, Seymour R. (Box 47, Folder 2116)
  - Lipson, Leon (Box 47, Folder 2117)
  - Litsey, David M. (Box 47, Folder 2118)
  - Litten, Jack D. (Box 47, Folder 2119)
  - Little, David (Box 47, Folder 2120)
  - Liu, Wu-Chi (Box 47, Folder 2121)
  - Livinston, Robert L. (Box 47, Folder 2122)
  - Loach, Donald G. (Box 47, Folder 2123)
  - Lockridge, Ernest H. (Box 47, Folder 2124)
  - Lockwood, Edward H. (Box 47, Folder 2125)
  - Lodge, George (Box 47, Folder 2126)
  - Lodge, John (Box 47, Folder 2127)
  - Logan, John A. (Box 47, Folder 2128)
  - Logue, Edward (Box 47, Folder 2129)
  - Lohmann, Carl A. (Box 47, Folder 2130)
  - Lolli, Giorgio (Box 47, Folder 2131)
  - London, George (Box 47, Folder 2132)
  - Long, C. N. Hugh (Box 47, Folder 2133)
  - Long, Charles (Box 47, Folder 2134)
  - Long, Herbert S. (Box 47, Folder 2135)
  - Long, W. Scott (Box 47, Folder 2136)
  - Longley, William E. (Box 47, Folder 2137)
  - Longley, William R. (Box 47, Folder 2138)
  - Longwell, Chester R. (Box 47, Folder 2139)
  - Loomis, Elias (Box 47, Folder 2140)
  - Loomis, James C. (Box 47, Folder 2141)
  - Looney, Charles T. G. (Box 47, Folder 2142)
  - Loosley, Robert O. (Box 47, Folder 2143)
  - Lopez, Claude A. (Box 47, Folder 2144)
  - Lopez, Robert S. (Box 47, Folder 2145)
  - Lord, Arthur (Box 47, Folder 2146)
  - Lord, Charles (Box 47, Folder 2147)
  - Lord, George De Forest (Box 48, Folder 2148)
  - Louden, Jonkheer (Box 48, Folder 2149)
  - Lounsbury, Floyd G. (Box 48, Folder 2150)
  - Lounsbury, Thomas R. (Box 48, Folder 2151)
  - Lovell, George Blakeman (Box 48, Folder 2152)
  - Lovell, Michael C. (Box 48, Folder 2153)
  - Lovett, Robert A. (Box 48, Folder 2154)
  - Lovett, Sidney (Box 48, Folder 2155)
  - Lowell, Robert (Box 48, Folder 2156)
  - Lowenstein, Allard (Box 48, Folder 2157)
  - Lowenstein, Hubertus Prince Zu (Box 48, Folder 2158)
  - Lowman, Robert, M.D. (Box 48, Folder 2159)
  - Lowry, Nelson, Jr. (Box 48, Folder 2160)
  - Luccock, Halford E. (Box 48, Folder 2161)
  - Luce, Henry R. (Box 48, Folder 2162)
  - Lucet, ----- (Box 48, Folder 2163)
  - Ludlum, David B., M.D. (Box 48, Folder 2164)
  - Ludwig, Frederick G. (Box 48, Folder 2165)
  - Lufkin, Paul (Box 48, Folder 2166)
  - Lukie, ----- (Box 48, Folder 2167)
  - Lull, Richard S. (Box 48, Folder 2168)
  - Lull, Timothy (Box 48, Folder 2169)
  - Luquiens, Jules (Box 48, Folder 2170)
  - Lustman, Seymour L. (Box 48, Folder 2171)
  - Lutz, Harold J. (Box 48, Folder 2172)
  - Lwowski, Walter (Box 48, Folder 2173)
  - Lydgate, Barry (Box 48, Folder 2174)
  - Lyman, Celtus (Box 48, Folder 2175)
  - Lyman, Chester S. (Box 48, Folder 2176)
  - Lyman, Joseph (Box 48, Folder 2177)
  - Lympany, Moura (Box 48, Folder 2178)
  - Lynch, Lincoln (Box 48, Folder 2179)
  - Lynd, Staughton (Box 48, Folder 2180)
  - Lynes, Russell (Box 48, Folder 2181)
  - Lyons, Philip A. (Box 48, Folder 2182)
  - Lytle, Art (Box 48, Folder 2183)
  - Lytton, Bernard (Box 48, Folder 2184)
  - Maas, James W. (Box 48, Folder 2185)
  - MacArthur, Douglas, II (Box 48, Folder 2186)
  - MacAvoy, Paul (Box 48, Folder 2187)
  - MacCurdy, George G. (Box 48, Folder 2188)
  - MacDonald, William L. (Box 49, Folder 2189)
  - MacFadden, Bruce J. (Box 49, Folder 2190)
  - Machlupet, Fritz (Box 49, Folder 2191)
  - Mack, Maynard (Box 49, Folder 2192)
  - MacKenzi, Ken (Box 49, Folder 2193)
  - MacLaine, Shirley (Box 49, Folder 2194)
  - MacLean, Burton A. (Box 49, Folder 2195)
  - MacLean, Jean (Box 49, Folder 2196)
  - MacLean, Paul D. (Box 49, Folder 2197)
  - MacLeish, Archibald (Box 49, Folder 2198)
  - MacLeish, William (Box 49, Folder 2199)
  - MacLeish, William H. (Box 49, Folder 2200)
  - MacLeman, Everett (Box 49, Folder 2201)
  - MacLennan, David A. (Box 49, Folder 2202)
  - MacLennan, Dorothy J. (Box 49, Folder 2203)
  - MacLeod, George (Box 49, Folder 2204)
  - MacMullan, Ramsay (Box 49, Folder 2205)
  - MacNeish, Richard Stockton (Box 49, Folder 2206)
  - MacVae, ----- (Socialist) (Box 49, Folder 2207)
  - Madison, Al (Box 49, Folder 2208)